<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Elegantly Kludgey</title><link>https://netpete.github.io/</link><description>Records of my development</description><atom:link href="https://netpete.github.io/rss.xml" type="application/rss+xml" rel="self"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 22:09:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>http://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2 in 1 Setup or How to get away with only 32GB</title><link>https://netpete.github.io/posts/2-in-1-setup-or-how-to-get-away-with-only-32gb.html</link><dc:creator>Peter Tiegs</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently decided to pick up a Windows machine and I really liked the idea of having a &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.intel.com/content/www/us/en/homepage.html"&gt;2 in 1&lt;/a&gt;.  So I did my research and purchased an &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://us.acer.com/ac/en/US/content/series/aspireswitch11"&gt;Acer&lt;/a&gt; Switch 11.  Overall I have been very happy with this little laptop/tablet.  Knowing that I would be using this for development I got the model with a 500GB HD in the keyboard.  Unfortunately this model only came with 32GB on the primary disk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My end goal was to be able to install &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.visualstudio.com"&gt;Visual Studio Community Edition&lt;/a&gt; on this machine for use in the Laptop mode, but not necessarily in tablet mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first thing I tried to do was to remove the recovery partition.  For some reason the OEM version of Windows provided with the Acer Switch did not allow for that.  Every time I tried to remove the partition it would prevent the OS from booting.  A quick Google search showed that this was a fairly common problem.  Fortunately I had a retail version Windows, so I hooked up a USB DVD drive and started from scratch.  I was able to create single partition for the OS and start the install.  Everything worked great...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...Almost, when the retail version of Windows booted the touch screen was no longer working.  So back to the Acer site and a quick download and install of the Intel platform drivers got everything back to working.  I still did not have Visual Studio installed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first attempted at installing Visual Studio to the D: drive failed.  While the primary interface was installed on the D: drive the bulk of the other content is still installed on the C: drive.  So I still need more space.  Next I added in a 64GB micro SD card and Robocopy'd my users directory to it.  To do this I created a local user with admin privileges and logged in as him. Then I removed the original home directory, and created a link to the home directory on the F: drive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class="code text"&gt;&lt;a name="rest_code_1f5235f634144df392ba8509aa1071ff-1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;robocopy /COPYALL /MIR /XJ c:\Users\Peter f:\Users\Peter
&lt;a name="rest_code_1f5235f634144df392ba8509aa1071ff-2"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;rd /S /Q c:\Users\Peter
&lt;a name="rest_code_1f5235f634144df392ba8509aa1071ff-3"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;mklink /J c:\Users\Peter f:\Users\Peter
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;When that was done I logged back in as myself, removed the local user and everything is working again.  But I still don't have a working version of Visual Studio.  I needed more space.  Then I downloaded &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://windirstat.info/"&gt;WinDirStat&lt;/a&gt; to analyze what was eating the most space.  It was the Visual Studio Package Cache in the ProgramData directory.  I had read that this was not something that should be removed and that it was needed for Visual Studio to work.  So I applied the same process that I used with my home directory to the package cache.  Robocopy the files to the D: drive, remove the files from the C: drive and link the D: drive files back to C: drive.  Now I was able to repair the installation of Visual Studio and fire it up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did this process two more times with the Windows SDKs and Microsoft Kits and now I have a healthy 3GB of the 32GB on the C: drive my users directory has over 50GB left on in and Visual Studio work when I am docked with the Keyboard and actually need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was always an extensive user of the &lt;code&gt;ln -s&lt;/code&gt; soft links in Posix operating system.  I am not sure when &lt;code&gt;mklink&lt;/code&gt; got added to the OS but I really appreciate the capabilities it provides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>https://netpete.github.io/posts/2-in-1-setup-or-how-to-get-away-with-only-32gb.html</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 17:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Getting Started with Github and Nikola</title><link>https://netpete.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-github-and-nikola.html</link><dc:creator>Peter Tiegs</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finally took the time to get set up with &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://pages.github.com/"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt; pages and &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://getnikola.com/"&gt;Nikola&lt;/a&gt; blogging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still a little curious how the git_hub deploy task works, and why it rquires multiple branches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking forward to trying out the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://ipython.org/"&gt;ipython&lt;/a&gt; notebook support and I would like to see if I can created some &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://pydoit.org/"&gt;doit&lt;/a&gt; tasks for publishing to &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.tumblr.com/"&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.jivesoftware.com/"&gt;Jive&lt;/a&gt; platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><guid>https://netpete.github.io/posts/getting-started-with-github-and-nikola.html</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 19:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>